To write about a flower,
to dramatize a flower,
I have to show the flower's arc.
And the flower's arc stretches back to the beginning of life.
How did this flower get here?
What was its journey?
Therefore,
I should infer from analogy
that probably all the organic beings which have ever lived on this earth
have descended from some one primordial form
into which life was first breathed.
It is a journey of evolution.
Adaptation.
The journey we all take.
A journey that unites each and every one of us.
Darwin writes that we all come from the very first single-cell organism.
Yet here I am.
And there's Laroche.
There's Orlean.
And there's the ghost orchid.
All trapped in our own bodies,
in moments in history.
That's it.
That's what I need to do.
Tie all of history together.
Start right before life begins on the planet.
All is...
lifeless.
And then, like, life begins,
um,
with organisms.
Those single-cell ones.
Oh, and it's before sex, because, like, everything was asexual.
From there we go to bigger things.
Jellyfish.
Then that fish that got legs and crawled out on the land.
And then we see, you know, like, dinosaurs.
Then they're around for a long time.
Then an asteroid comes and "phwar!"
The insects, the mammals, the primates, monkeys.
The simple monkeys.
The old-fashioned monkeys giving way to the new monkeys.
Whatever. And then apes. Whatever. And man.
Then we see the whole history of human civilization,
hunting, gathering, farming, war, love, religion, heartache, disease, loneliness, technology.
We bring it all the way to this moment in history and
end with Susan Orlean in her office at The New Yorker
writing about flowers, and bang!
The movie begins.
This is great.
This is the breakthrough I've been hoping for.
It's never been ...
She's a genius!