I want to do one more excercise.
It's like a role play.
My role ...
Is ..
All the thoughts that provoke your fear ...
Yours ...
is rational thinking.
I am nature ...
All the things that you call nature.
Okay Mr.Nature
what do you want?
To hurt you as much as I can.
How?
How do you think?
By Frightening me?
By killing you.
Nature can't hurt me.
You just told you're the green in the outside...
No, I'm more than that.
I don't understand.
I'm outside, but also...
within
I'm nature of all human beings
Oh, That kind of nature.
The kind of nature that...
Causes people do the evil things against women
That's exactly who I am.
That kind of nature interested me a lot.
When I was uphere
That kind of nature was the subject to my thesis...
But you shouldn't underestimate Eden.
What did Eden do?
I discovered somethng else in my material than I expected.
If human nature is evil...
Then that goes as well...
That the nature...
of the women.
Female nature.
The nature of all the sisters.
Women do not control their own bodies
Nature does.
I have it in writing in my books.
The literature you used Nin your office search...
Was about evil things committed against women.
But you read it as proof of the evil of women?
You were supposed to be critical of those says. That was your thesis
Instead you're embracing it
Do you know what you're saying?
Forget it.
I do not know why I said it.
It can't work anymore now.